<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[O21] Rimhammer 40K (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.O21Rimhammer40K</packageId>
  <author>Neronix17</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/O21Rimhammer40K</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
      <displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/UnlimitedHugs/RimworldHugsLib/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
      <displayName>JecsTools</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2195729899</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>neronix17.toolbox</packageId>
      <displayName>[O21] Toolbox</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/1660622094</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>XeoNovaDan.TurretExtensions</packageId>
      <displayName>[XND] Turret Extensions</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2201064941</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>Mlie.FillBackstories</packageId>
      <displayName>Fill backstories</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2407610901</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
    <li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
    <li>neronix17.toolbox</li>
    <li>XeoNovaDan.TurretExtensions</li>
    <li>Mlie.FillBackstories</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of Neronix17s mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1513943591
with their permission

Neronix17 is currently working on a reworked version of this mod that is scheduled to be released in the summer of 2021

- Since some parts of the mod depended on removed features they had to be remade, hopfully without errors
- I have personally no experience with the Warhammer 40K universe so any questions regarding the lore I leave to the fans to answer
- Some of the factions should now no longer be permanent enemies with the empire. They will however almost always be enemies from the start since they have negative goodwill. Thanks flameroran77 for info on what factions to modify!

- The story-framework the original mod used is not updated but it was only used for some tutorial message:

[h2]Building tutorial[/h2]
To avoid clogging up the build menu we've come up with a solution in Rimhammer 40k using the same style of selection as most things in vanilla have for selecting the material you build with, in this case you'll be using it to choose specifically what you want to make out of a type of object. So when it comes to Necrons it's simply used to choose the colour of gauss crystals you use and thus the colour of the energy visually shown on the structure as a whole.
All factions use this, so keep an eye out for the little mark like in the image on icons when building, you might have been missing something when it was right in front of you the whole time.

[h2]Races tutorial[/h2]
Races in Rimhammer 40k sometimes have specific restrictions placed on the equipment they use to prevent others from using it. A few examples are Tau, Space Marines, Eldar and Sisters of Battle. 
There are others but it's good to keep this in mind when checking what equipment you want to make, be sure to check their stats for any restrictions placed on them. This is done usually because it happens to be the only body shape available for the race and allowing the clothing on any other race would just make it show up as a big pink square or the texture just would look ridiculous on them.
Along with racial restrictions some items may have other types of restriction, such as body type for apparel, or requiring a specific piece of apparel to work such as a back mounted promethium tank to use a heavy flamer. These are also listed in the stats of the items.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/O21Rimhammer40K][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]
[h1]Rimhammer 40K mod for Rimworld[/h1]
Adds objects, factions and more from the WarHammer universe.

[h1]Credits[/h1]
[list]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/durge13/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Neronix17[/url] - Mostly of the code, and some textures.
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198087553011/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Ods[/url] - Hairs from mod [Ods] Mens Hair , and many of the art assets, primarily pawn equipment and races themselves.
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/krnoel85/myworkshopfiles/]KinKade[/url] - Many textures and some of the XML code, primarily structures, security and other buildings, along with creatures and some of the pawn equipment and races.
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198053225215/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Krysismode[/url] - Helps a lot with brainstorming, moderating and generally being a great guy.
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197973673941/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Albion[/url] - Provided a large chunk of the C # code that was the original basis for the conversion pods. Check out his amazing Sparkling Worlds - Full Mod!
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/chickenplcker/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Chicken Pluckston[/url] - Hair assets, can be found for non Imperial Guard humans here along with other mods he has made. CP has also provided quite a few other assets to the mod including map icons and help with balancing.
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/Syrchalis/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Syrchalis[/url] - Recaf Leaf textures.
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198021336326/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Rikiki[/url] - MiningCo Mods .
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/spdskatr/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Spdsktr[/url] - Project RimFactory.
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/erdelf/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]erdelf[/url] - Humanoid Alien Races 2.0 .
[/list]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>
